<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on Fogify: A Fog Computing Emulator Framework</title>
    <link>https://ucy-linc-lab.github.io/fogify/installation.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on Fogify: A Fog Computing Emulator Framework</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ucy-linc-lab.github.io/fogify/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fogify in Docker-compose</title>
      <link>https://ucy-linc-lab.github.io/fogify/installation/as-a-service.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ucy-linc-lab.github.io/fogify/installation/as-a-service.html</guid>
      <description>Execution To ease the installation of Fogify, we created a docker-compose file that contains a dockerized version of Fogify connected with a Jupyter server, which is used as a web-based GUI. Since, the Fogify and Jupyter stack is provided as dockerized services, we only need to run the following command at the swarm master node.
 Copy    sudo docker-compose -p fogemulator up    In order to open the web interface of Jupyter, you have to find the output of the ui service where the system outputs the url and the token</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bare-metal Installation</title>
      <link>https://ucy-linc-lab.github.io/fogify/installation/bare-metal.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ucy-linc-lab.github.io/fogify/installation/bare-metal.html</guid>
      <description>Dependencies When we have installed the expected software components, now we have to install the main components of the Fogify System. Since Fogify is developed with python, firstly, we install the python libraries with the following command (on each Cluster Node): Copy    sudo pip3 install -r requirements.txt    Fogify Controller (Master) The Fogify Controller should run on the Cluster&amp;rsquo;s Manager Node. The Controller will receive any request and will communicate to the other nodes (Fogify Agents) in order to disseminate the appropriate commands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
